{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "In &quot;One Piece&quot;, what does &quot;the Pirate King&quot; mean to the captain of the Straw Hat Pirates?",
      "correct_answer": "Freedom",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Promise",
        "Adventure",
        "Friendship"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "Which animation studio produced &quot;Log Horizon&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Satelite",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Sunrise",
        "Xebec",
        "Production I.G"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "In the anime Initial D, how does Takumi Fujiwara describe a drift?",
      "correct_answer": "&#039;. . . the front tires slide so the car won&#039;t face the inside&#039;",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "&#039;. . . the wheels lose traction, making the car slide sideways&#039;",
        "&#039;. . . the car oversteers through a curve, causing it to turn faster&#039;",
        "&#039;. . . you turn a lot&#039;"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "Which song was the callsign for Stefan Verdemann&#039;s KWFM radio station in Urasawa Naoki&#039;s &quot;Monster&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Over the Rainbow",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "What a Wonderful World",
        "When You Wish Upon A Star",
        "Singing In The Rain"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "Which one of these characters is from &quot;Legendz : Tale of the Dragon Kings&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Shiron",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Jack",
        "Axia",
        "Drum"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "In the anime, Full Metal Panic!, who is Kaname&#039;s best friend?",
      "correct_answer": "Kyoko Tokiwa",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Melissa Mao",
        "Ren Mikihara",
        "Teletha &quot;Tessa&quot; Testarossa"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "In &quot;One Piece&quot;, who confirms the existence of the legendary treasure, One Piece?",
      "correct_answer": "Edward &quot;Whitebeard&quot; Newgate",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Former Marine Fleet Admiral Sengoku",
        "Pirate King Gol D Roger",
        "Silvers Rayleigh"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "Which person from &quot;JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure&quot; does NOT house a reference to a band, artist, or song earlier than 1980?",
      "correct_answer": "Giorno Giovanna",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Josuke Higashikata",
        "Jolyne Cujoh",
        "Johnny Joestar"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "Which animation studio animated &quot;Hidamari Sketch&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Shaft",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Trigger",
        "Kyoto Animation",
        "Production I.G"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "In which manga did the &quot;404 Girl&quot; from 4chan originate from?",
      "correct_answer": "Yotsuba&amp;!",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Azumanga Daioh",
        "Lucky Star",
        "Clover"
      ]
    }
  ]
}